whole families nuts my mom just joined
Facebook two months ago so that's my was
I've been dealing with for a while she
has no sense of sarcasm she's realized
people put funny pictures on Facebook
she thinks they're all real came home
one day and the cat was passed out in a
weird way so put an empty beer can right
next to him put that picture on Facebook
she was the first comment within seconds
it just said mark beer is very bad for
cats
then she liked her own comment I was
like you're doing this wrong and I'm
gonna block you I don't care god bless
her she's trying she's got all the
technology you know she's doing the
iPhone the iPad she's skyping with the
grandkids you know mostly we look at her
thumb but it's going way it's funny it's
funny sometimes to watch old people try
to figure out technology you know you
catch some of the corny or I know some
old lady trying to unlock her car you
know with her cell phone one time I saw
an old lady trying to get money out of a
red box you know she was convinced it
was an ATM she just kept looking around
going oh what money why does it keep
giving me movies it's priceless but the
best of all time I was in Montana
getting gas you get out of my car and I
hear all this commotion down the way and
I look and there's an old man screaming
at the gas pump like it was some kind of
futuristic robot going yeah hey gas in
my car
what's happening and then I hear the guy
in the gas station he's like I said come
in here in here and I'll explain how to
do it
this guy's like coming he picked up the
nozzle he was like hello this phone
smells like gas
I step back and enjoy it for a while but
then I realize it was time to help when
he was signed it trying to slide a check
into the credit card swiper house like
sir I can't go off the rest of my day
knowing that you're still here screaming
at this gas pump please let me help you
you know the best part of the whole
story is I come over you know all
magnanimous like this young guy that's
gonna help this old man and it turns out
he has a car from the 70s where the gas
tank is hidden behind the back license
plate I don't know if you guys have seen
this car before couple of you will nod
their heads never seen in my life we're
just wandering around the car together
like we're against pushing taillights
and hubcaps I actually said out loud at
one point is this a DeLorean
I haven't seen one of those I had to
walk away he's like well thanks a lot
idiot I was like what are you getting
mad at me for you know the guy bought a
car without a gas thank you baby
did you get roped in the van old man sir
I got the car for you it's called a
Chevy one runs out of gas leave it on
the side of the road we'll find it yeah
my my dad was like the total grumpy old
man after he he worked for Wells Fargo
for 50 years and he retired his favorite
thing in retirement returning things to
stores I don't know I brought him so
much joy he actually had a thing called
the switcheroo if you guys have ever
pulled the switcheroo before but it was
legendary in our house if something
broke we would not throw it away I
damned if I know what it is go to the
store purchase the exact same product
bring it home take the new one out
replace it with the broken one
immediately return it and get his money
back dude that is horrible he's like I'm
sticking it to the man
house I think you're just stealing
but he never got caught ever he got so
brazen he tried to return a 10 year old
showerhead legendary story my mom's
having some back stuff he goes buys this
new one
got all the massager settings on it's
three times the size of the old shower
head he's taken down the old one which I
assume came with the house it's all
rusted and mildewed he puts them in this
plastic snap case that the new one came
in
there's no packaging you can just see it
rattling around in there I just assume
he's throwing everything away when he's
done installing it he goes alright I
gotta head back to the store and I was
like pardon because you know what just
let me do my thing
I was like what I got I gotta go with
you on this one again I gotta watch this
go down yeah so I hang back he goes up
the return counter he puts the shower
head the receipt the guy looks at it and
he looks at my head and he looks at it
he goes sir I don't get it this is
obviously an old rusted mildewed shower
head and my dad is confident as I've
ever seen him just makes eye contact and
he goes imagine my surprise when I got
it home
and he got the money he took me out to
lunch on that money hey folks I just
wanted to say thank you for watching my
clips so you can watch my entire special
for 99 cents which i think is a good
deal you can watch more clips by
clicking here yeah I mean click it why
are you just staring at me I'm a pretty
weird-looking dude so I would click
faster than wait just click it right now